Delete remote themes from the connected store. This command can't be undone.

USAGE
  $ shopify theme delete [-d] [-e <value>...] [-f] [--no-color]
    [--password <value>] [--path <value>] [-a] [-s <value>] [-t <value>...]
    [--verbose]

FLAGS
  -a, --show-all                Include others development themes in theme list.
  -d, --development             Delete your development theme.
  -e, --environment=<value>...  The environment to apply to the current command.
  -f, --force                   Skip confirmation.
  -s, --store=<value>           Store URL. It can be the store prefix (example)
                                or the full myshopify.com URL
                                (example.myshopify.com,
                                https://example.myshopify.com).
  -t, --theme=<value>...        Theme ID or name of the remote theme.
      --no-color                Disable color output.
      --password=<value>        Password generated from the Theme Access app or
                                an Admin API token.
      --path=<value>            The path where you want to run the command.
                                Defaults to the current working directory.
      --verbose                 Increase the verbosity of the output.

DESCRIPTION
  Delete remote themes from the connected store. This command can't be undone.

  Deletes a theme from your store.

  You can specify multiple themes by ID. If no theme is specified, then you're
  prompted to select the theme that you want to delete from the list of themes
  in your store.

  You're asked to confirm that you want to delete the specified themes before
  they are deleted. You can skip this confirmation using the `--force` flag.

